Kurtis Gibb

Thunder Bay, Ontario kurtisgibb@outlook.com

SUMMARY

Full Stack Developer with a strong desire to continuously learn new technologies. Many years of living in Visual Studio and SSMS. I have been building out projects using reactjs and more recently learning about nextjs. Outside of work I am a highly competitive person and as such spend most of my time competing wherever I can.

EDUCATION

Computer Programming | Confederation College SEPTEMBER 2014 – APRIL 2016

Gained the technical skills necessary to develop software in a variety of languages. Desktop applications, mobile applications and web applications were developed in a variety of tools such as .NET C#, VB .NET, Java, JavaScript, php, SQL, and NativeScript. Learned about the software development cycle, design patterns, user experience strategies, design techniques, non-language specific development skills, testing, and hosting. Attended a startup weekend which involved developing a project to present in 54 hours.

EXPERIENCE

Systems Analyst | Health e(fx)

JUNE 2018 - CURRENT

Integral in assuring company software solutions are working to meet the client needs. Work includes, but is not limited to, creating custom report, providing solutions to ensure the system handles client data, identifying issues with software solutions and finding or reporting resolutions, creating impact analysis's for system or client specific issues.

Business Application Programmer/Analyst | City of Thunder Bay APRIL 2016 – JANUARY 2018

Responsible for end-to-end application development. Worked on projects both independently, and as a team. Worked on web applications for external and internal use. Built services and desktop applications for city departments. Provided tier 3 support for all applications that I implemented into production.

COMPUTER PROGRAMMER | Aurora

SEPTEMBER 2015 – JANUARY 2016

Created custom UI's in Java. Spent time researching functional programming in Scala and creating learning material around the subject.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- SQL, MSSQL, PL/SQL
- ASP.NET (Web Forms & MVC), .NET Desktop Applications (VB.NET & C#)
- Java, Scala, Eclipse
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript (ES5, ES6), React, Bootstrap, Semantic, MaterialUI
- Git, GitHub